[
      {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 41 and height 77?",
      "correctAnswer": "1578.5",
      "options": [
        "1578.5",
        "1581.0",
        "1582.5",
        "1576.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 64 and height 27?",
      "correctAnswer": "864.0",
      "options": [
        "866.5",
        "864.0",
        "861.5",
        "868.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 25 and height 38?",
      "correctAnswer": "475.0",
      "options": [
        "472.5",
        "475.0",
        "479.0",
        "477.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 26 and height 51?",
      "correctAnswer": "663.0",
      "options": [
        "667.0",
        "665.5",
        "660.5",
        "663.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 40 and height 68?",
      "correctAnswer": "1360.0",
      "options": [
        "1357.5",
        "1362.5",
        "1360.0",
        "1364.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 1 and height 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "7.0",
      "options": [
        "7.0",
        "9.5",
        "4.5",
        "11.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 12 and height 37?",
      "correctAnswer": "222.0",
      "options": [
        "222.0",
        "224.5",
        "226.0",
        "219.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 73 and height 55?",
      "correctAnswer": "2007.5",
      "options": [
        "2007.5",
        "2010.0",
        "2005.0",
        "2011.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 73 and height 42?",
      "correctAnswer": "1533.0",
      "options": [
        "1535.5",
        "1533.0",
        "1537.0",
        "1530.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 44 and height 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "88.0",
      "options": [
        "85.5",
        "88.0",
        "90.5",
        "92.0"
      ]
    }
]